[{"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "IULIANI (R), FORMER NYC MAYOR (via telephone): How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Was that coincidence?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to have to see.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Is he the best candidate for this job, do you think?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Given the data that is coming out in the last 48 hours about jobs, about house prices and so on, do you believe now that this will be determined, as it often is, about the economy?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Is the time coming when you need to say yes or no?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I have a different view than Donald.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "What would yours be?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "No, I never said that.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you stand by that now?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I wouldn't consider running with anybody at this point.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Would you ever consider running with her, Rudy?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well, I know Anthony from the time that he was a city council member and I was a mayor back in 1994.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What is going on here, do you think?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "That's the point.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "How many times did he take pictures like that that he can't remember whether he took it or not?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "First of all, I think they had every right to take them to the baseball game.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Was he right to do that?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I'm quite well, thank you.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Wanda, how are you?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, I had all these sort of carefully choreographed questions for you -- the usual kind of stuff.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "And you?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I just want to say I am very flattered that when it comes to sex scandals, that you thought of me because usually people don't go, Wanda Sykes, let's talk sex.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "You know, first -- OK, here's the thing.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What do you think of Weiner-gate?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I tweet now.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Do you believe it?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "No yet.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Have you found any yet?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Are you ever shocked by the sheer volume of sex scandals of politicians in particular?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Because they're -- one, they're people in power.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Why do they all do this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "We talking about his movies or as a person?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Sometimes I think that they want to get caught, you know.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What is it about -- I mean, we've talked about men in powerful positions, but what is it about the risk taking that goes on, do you think?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "A lot of my good friends, they're men.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "ORGAN: I mean, what do you think of men?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I think all people are susceptible to temptation.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Do you think all men are susceptible to temptation?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I'm still rooting for the black president.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "How's he doing, the half white guy?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I mean, having said that, we have the big Bin Laden thing recently --", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Let's just go blow stuff up, you know?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "YKES: I think it's -- OK, I think it's less racist because we elected an African-American president.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Do you think that America is more or less racist since it's had its first African-American president?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Where were you born, right.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "No one's ever asked any white political leader, where were you born?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I would throw Donald Trump in there, too.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "So whether they intended it or not, the birther crowd, you know, I don't think Donald Trump's a racist for a moment, but I think a lot of people that latched onto that campaign was certainly bordering on racism, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What is it -- what is it based on if it's not race?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Come on, Piers.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "That's better.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Is that better?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Yes, I believe that.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Do you really think it's harder to be gay than black?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "But today -- now I'm not talking about the history of, you know, black people -- African-Americans.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Just right now in American for example -- harder to be gay in America than be black?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know of organizations and groups, you know, like Focus on the Family and such -- you know, anti-gay organizations who are putting up so much money, millions and millions of dollars into stopping me from, you know, being black or telling me that I can't, you know, exercise my blackness or whatever.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Am I right in saying that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Um, liberated and also it wasn't an in your face.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "As you got up to make it, knowing what you were about to do, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Best thing is just now that there's this -- not that I was hiding before, but now there is absolutely nothing to hide.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "What was the best and worst thing about coming out for you, when you look back over the period since?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Much better.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How are things now?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I think time.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What has helped that process?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "There you go.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Give them six hours to think about this before we have to talk again, right?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Were you very nervous about making that call?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "They said they didn't.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Do you think either of your parents knew?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Well, it was good.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "When he went through his point by point guide to how much he had achieved, what was your reaction, good and bad?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Hesitant.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Can I get a fancy book?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think he's doing it the right way.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "If you're being overly critical, what would you say is -- he could have been pushed a bit harder?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "It must be great fun to make, isn't it?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "It's like constant rolling improv, right?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Richard Pryor.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Who is the single funniest comedian you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "His humanity, you know.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "And what made him such a genius?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I love Ricky.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Where is the line, do you think, in that?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Laughs.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What is the reward that you like most from the work?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "A live laugh.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "A live laugh?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "She does, yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Does she speak French?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "You didn't talk to her on the ferry?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I was walking along with my friend.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "And then you met her where, at a party?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "No, but I was drunk.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Did you remember her from the ferry?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "I'm very happy.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "And now that whoever that person was has stepped in, are you happy?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I'm very well, thank you.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Christy, how are you?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "You don't really like being called a super model, do you?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "I don't know really what it means.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Well, it's my older sister.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "How did that happen?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Well, we did a lot of trips in the early couple of years that we were together, white water rafting and ski trips and different things.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "And then the rest of the Burns boys come into play?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Now that you're a director, is he feeling a little bit threatened?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Well, I had my first child about seven and a half years ago.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Why did you make this documentary?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "Yes, director, financier, producer, writer.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Are you the director?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Well, I can't say I have any training as a documentarian.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "But where did you get this skill?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "Well, that there's hope, that a lot of the solutions, we know what they are.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "What's the most important thing that you hope people take away from this film?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "You went to college at 25?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Yes, a liberal arts degree, but I focused on comparative religion and eastern philosophy.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "And you came out with an arts degree?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "Well, you know.", "docId": "110602pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "ORGAN: So quite a smart cookie, aren't you?", "qSentId": 795}]